<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pasta on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/pasta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pasta on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/pasta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Goulash With Ground Beef</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</guid>
      <description>Quick Goulash Recipe with Fresh Ground Beef and Elbow Macaroni, Tomato Sauce and Fresh Cut Vegetables with Cheese. Goulash is a Great Casserole for Lunch or Supper.
Goulash serves 8
 1 lb macaroni, cooked 8 min., drained 1 lb ground beef, cooked, drained 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 can tomato sauce 1 can diced tomatoes 2 oz. melted butter 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp chili powder 1 c shredded cheddar cheese(optional)  Combine all ingredients in large mixing bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Ingredients Serves 4
 1 lb shrimp, raw, peeled, deveined, (size of your choice) 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 lb fresh sliced mushrooms 1 tsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 onion, diced 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tsp olive oil 2 lbs. angel hair pasta  Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Directions Place pan of water on stove med. high heat to boil water, add a small amount of salt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Vegetarian Goulash</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-vegetarian-goulash/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-vegetarian-goulash/</guid>
      <description>vegetarian goulash is a delicious recipe made with tomato sauce, pasta, fresh cut vegetables and cheese. Great for Lunch or Supper and can be served with salads, vegetables, fruit, and hot rolls with honey butter.
Vegetarian Goulash Ingredients Serves 8
 1 lb macaroni, cooked 8 min., drained 1 tsp. olive oil 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 rib celery, diced small 1 12oz. can tomato sauce 1 12oz.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
