<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kids on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/kids/</link><description>Recent content in Kids on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/kids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Macaroni and Cheese Recipe For 200</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/macaroni-and-cheese-recipe-for-200/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/macaroni-and-cheese-recipe-for-200/</guid><description>Quick Institutional Macaroni and Cheddar Cheese Recipe is the Favorite of most Kids. Macaroni and Cheddar Cheese from Scratch is great with Fresh Watermelon and Salads. A Warm Roll is Nice too!
Macaroni and Cheese with Cheddar for 240 people Prep time: 30 minutes
Cook time: 30 minutes
Serves: 240
Ingredients 30# elbo macaroni 25# shredded cheddar cheese (medium or sharp) 2 lbs melted butter 1 1/2 gallons milk 2 tbsp salt 2 tbsp pepper Directions In large kettle or two kettles, place macaroni in boiling water, stir frequently to keep from sticking.</description></item><item><title>All Sweet Nut Cookies</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/dessert-recipes/all-sweet-nut-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/dessert-recipes/all-sweet-nut-cookies/</guid><description>Sandy’s allsweet nut cookies are fun and easy to make. A great snack for kids after school or anytime. Get the kids to help make these delicious cookies.
Sandy’s Allsweet Nut Cookies 1/2 c. margerine softened 2 tsp sugar 1 c. chopped pecans 1 tsp. vanilla 7/8 c. sifted flour 2 c. powdered sugar set aside (for rolling cookies after baking) Allsweet Nut Cookies Directions Cream margarine and sugar together.</description></item><item><title>Apple Smackers Recipe</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/dessert-recipes/apple-smackers-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/dessert-recipes/apple-smackers-recipe/</guid><description>Apple Smackers Recipe Serves 4
3 tart apples 3 tbsp sugar 1/2 tbsp cinnamon 2 0z. butter, melted Apple Smackers Directions Peel apples and cut in wedges. Place wedges on microwaveable plate. Brush melted butter over apples. Combine sugar with cinnamon, then sprinkle over apples. Cover with wax paper or plastic wrap and place in microwave for about 5 minutes. Check for tenderness. Eat em up.</description></item></channel></rss>