<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sauces on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>/tags/sauces/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sauces on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:30:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/sauces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recipe Basics and Sauces</title>
      <link>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Recipe Basics Section of our site. Recipe Basics Partner and Link With Other Recipes on This Site. A Convenient and Quick way to Coordinate your Family Menu Plans. For Example, Maitre d’ Butter Goes with Sirloin Steak., Easy Basic Sauce Recipes, Easy Internal Links to the Roux Recipe, Egg Washfor your Fruit Pie Crusts so your Pie Crust is Flaky. Drawn Butter, for Fresh Seafood Recipes like Lobster Thermidorand Broiled Whitefishfrom Lake Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coney Sauce Recipe</title>
      <link>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/coney-sauce-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/coney-sauce-recipe/</guid>
      <description>This Quick Easy Coney Sauce is Chef Frank’s Original Recipe. Use over High Grade Hot Dogs with Vadalia Onions and make other Lunches Jealous. Coney Sauce is a great Starter for ChiliToo.
Coney Sauce Chef Frank’s Original Recipe  2 lbs ground beef chuck or sirloin 1/2 small vadalia(sweet) onion diced 1 clove garlic, peeled, crushed or 1 tbs garlic powder (more or less to taste) 2 tbs tomato paste 1/2 tsp salt 1/2 tsp white pepper 4 tbs ground cumin (cumino)  Coney Sauce Directions In large frying pan brown ground beef with onions, garlic, cumin, salt and pepper, breaking up burger as it cooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delicious Homemade Teriyaki Chicken</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/delicious-homemade-teriyaki-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/delicious-homemade-teriyaki-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Teriyaki chicken with homemade sauce contains pineapple, garlic, brown sugar and soy sauce. It’s great for the barbecue grill outside, or inside under your broiler. Teriyaki chicken can be served with wild rice, salads or fruits or all the above.
Great on the barbecue grill!
Teriyaki Chicken Ingredients serves 4-6
 2 whole chickens cut in 1/8’s, fresh 2 c Teriyaki sauce (see recipe below) 1 tbs. Chef Frank’s Seasoning  Method #1 In large roasting pan, place chicken, seasoning, and teriyaki sauce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Prime Rib Roast with Au Jus</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/holiday-prime-rib-roast-with-au-jus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/holiday-prime-rib-roast-with-au-jus/</guid>
      <description>Celebrate the Holidays with our very special Prime Rib Roast recipe. It includes an awesome Au Jus recipe. Follow the links to festive side dishes too.
Prime Rib Roast Ingredients  15-19 lb rib roast 1/4 c garlic, fresh chopped 1 tbsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 c water  Prime Rib Directions Place rib roast in large roasting pan, bone down, add water and seasonings. Cover and place in oven at 275* and roast for 5 hours then check with thermometer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Barbecue Country Ribs</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</guid>
      <description>Chef Frank’s honey barbecue country ribs are slow cooked until tender and will wow your family and friends at yourback yard Barbecue.
Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Ingredients  3 lb country pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 to 2 c honey barbecue sauce 1/2 c water  Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning. Cover and roast at 275* for 2 -1/2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</guid>
      <description>Chef Frank’s Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs are so delicious and easy to prepare in the oven or on the barbecue grill. Great with roasted red potatoesand salador fruit.
Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Ingredients  3 lb or more baby back pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 c honey barbecue sauce 1 c barbecue sauce (if you prefer regular barbecue sauce without honey) 1/2 c water  Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Our honey teriyaki barbecue sauce will become a staple in your recipe file. It’s easy to prepare on the stove and great for the barbecue grillfor ribs, chicken, chops and steaks.
Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce Ingredients  2 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 3 tbsp soy sauce 1 c pineapple juice ( or 1 c, pureed fresh pineapple) 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses 2 tbsp grape jelly  Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour or until reduced, stirring frequently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Michigan Broiled Whitefish</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/lake-michigan-broiled-whitefish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/lake-michigan-broiled-whitefish/</guid>
      <description>Let’s have broiled whitefish from Lake Michigan. Simply place on foil pie pan, butter, season, and broil. Serve with drawn butter or tartar sauce. Serve with any side dish, salad, rice, or potato.
Broiled Whitefish Ingredients  1 disposable. pie tin 9″-10″ 2 fresh whitefish (preferred from Lake Michigan) 2oz. butter melted couple shakes of Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 lemon 2 oz. water  Broiled Whitefish Directions Place whitefish in pan, then add water (do not spray pan as skin will come off when cooked).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffed Pork Loin Recipe</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Stuffed pork loin with fresh raspberry sauce is a wonderful Holiday or Fall entree. The stuffing can be made with either walnuts or pecans. for presentation, slice and shingle onto a platter or tray.
Stuffed Pork Loin With Raspberry Sauce Stuffing:  4 c water 2tsp chicken base 1/2 lg. onion diced 2 ribs celery diced 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tbsp sage 2 apples, peeled, diced 1/2 stick butter 1 c chopped pecans  Place all ingredients above in medium sauce pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tartar Sauce For Fish</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tartar-sauce-for-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tartar-sauce-for-fish/</guid>
      <description>Quick Easy Tartar Sauce Recipe makes fish meals complete. With a touch of lemon, Tartar Sauce is great with Fried Clams or Walleye, and Fish and Chips.
Tartar Sauce Ingredients  1 c mayonaise or salad dressing 1/2 c sweet pickle relish 1 -2 tbsp lemon juice 1/2 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning  Tartar Sauce Directions Mix ingredients together well, serve with fish and other seafoods. Refrigerate, covered.
Note: Did you know that by adding 1/4 c ketchup to this recipe you have a great Thousand Island sauce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuna Noodle Casserole</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Tuna Noodle Casserole is a Family Favorite and is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare. Our Creamy Tuna Noodle Casserole is Comfort Food for those Cold Winter Days.
Tuna Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
 8 oz, tuna, drained 1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux  Tuna Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarian Honey Barbecue Sauce</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/vegetarian-honey-barbecue-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/vegetarian-honey-barbecue-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Prepare this vegetarian honey barbecue sauce recipe when you’re grilling outside or cooking inside. It makes your vegetarian burgers, and ribs taste amazing.
Vegetarian Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients  1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses  Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
