<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Casserole Recipes on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Casserole Recipes on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:19:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick Beef Stew</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/quick-beef-stew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 22:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/quick-beef-stew/</guid>
      <description>Quick Beef Stew will warm your heart and tummy. Beef Stew with vegetables and thick gravy is great with biscuits and a salad or fruit. Beef Stew always makes good leftovers.
Beef Stew Recipe serves4-6
 1 lb diced beef 2 large carrots 2 ribs celery 1 lg onion 3-4 lg potatoes 1 tbsp beef base garlic, salt &amp;amp; pepper to taste  Directions Clean and cut vegetables into desired size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Sweet Potato Casserole</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/healthy-sweet-potato-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/healthy-sweet-potato-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Potato Casserole with Michigan Apples and Cranberries Compliment Porkand Chicken EntreeDishes. An easy Side Dish for Get Togethers with Family and Friends or for the Holidays.
Sweet Potato Casserole with Michigan Apples and Cranberries Ingredients serves10-12
 6 large sweet potatoes( peeled cut in chunks) 1 lb fresh cranberries 3 large Michigan apples (peeled and cut bite size) 2 c apple juice or cider  Directions Put ingredients in baking dish, cover, and bake 350℉ for 1 hour</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Green Bean Casserole</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/simple-green-bean-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/simple-green-bean-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Quick Green Bean Casserole is a standard Recipe used for Holidays and everyday meals. Green Bean Casserole topped with Fried Onions and Cheese will Shake Up your Meals!A Simple and Healthy Green Bean CasseroleGreen Bean Casserole Ingredients *serves 8 -10℉
 2 cans green beans, drained 1 can cream of mushroom soup 1/2 c shredded or diced cheddar cheese (optional) 2 tbsp melted butter French fried onions  Directions Mix green beans with undiluted mushroom soup and melted butter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Noodle Casserole</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Noodle Casserole, Quick Recipe for Lunch or Dinner Entree. Chicken Noodle Casserole is True Comfort Food and goes with any Salad, Fruit, and Warm Bread.
Chicken Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
 1 lb cooked chicken meat cut up1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank&amp;rsquo;s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux  Chicken Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creamy Scalloped Potatoes</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/creamy-scalloped-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/creamy-scalloped-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Quick Creamy Scalloped Potatoes, Great Comfort Food Entree on those Cold Winter Days. Warm up the House with a Creamy Scalloped Potato Aroma.
Creamy Scalloped Potatoes serves 8
 3# red potatoes, sliced 1/4″ 1/2 onion, diced 3 ribs celery, diced small 3 c milk 1 c roux 1 tsp chicken base 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 oz. butter  Creamy Scalloped Potatoes Directions Boil potatoes in medium size pot for about 20 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goulash With Ground Beef</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</guid>
      <description>Quick Goulash Recipe with Fresh Ground Beef and Elbow Macaroni, Tomato Sauce and Fresh Cut Vegetables with Cheese. Goulash is a Great Casserole for Lunch or Supper.
Goulash serves 8
 1 lb macaroni, cooked 8 min., drained 1 lb ground beef, cooked, drained 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 can tomato sauce 1 can diced tomatoes 2 oz. melted butter 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp chili powder 1 c shredded cheddar cheese(optional)  Combine all ingredients in large mixing bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalloped Potatoes – Grandma’s Comfort Food</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/scalloped-potatoes-grandmas-comfort-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/scalloped-potatoes-grandmas-comfort-food/</guid>
      <description>Quick Scalloped Potatoes is Grandma’s recipe and will satisfy any appetite. Add ham to this Scalloped Potato recipe for a wonderful comfort food a cold winter day.
Scalloped Potatoes Ingredients  Scalloped Potatoes 6 potatoes, peeled, thin sliced 1/2 onion, diced 2 rib celery, diced 4 oz. butter, melted 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 cups flour 3 cups milk  Scalloped Potatoes Directions In large casserole dish, place a layer of potatoes in bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuna Noodle Casserole</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Tuna Noodle Casserole is a Family Favorite and is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare. Our Creamy Tuna Noodle Casserole is Comfort Food for those Cold Winter Days.
Tuna Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
 8 oz, tuna, drained 1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux  Tuna Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
