<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Easy on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/easy/</link><description>Recent content in Easy on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/easy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Goulash With Ground Beef</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</guid><description>Quick Goulash Recipe with Fresh Ground Beef and Elbow Macaroni, Tomato Sauce and Fresh Cut Vegetables with Cheese. Goulash is a Great Casserole for Lunch or Supper.
Goulash serves 8
1 lb macaroni, cooked 8 min., drained 1 lb ground beef, cooked, drained 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 can tomato sauce 1 can diced tomatoes 2 oz. melted butter 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp chili powder 1 c shredded cheddar cheese(optional) Combine all ingredients in large mixing bowl.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</guid><description>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Ingredients Serves 4
1 lb shrimp, raw, peeled, deveined, (size of your choice) 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 lb fresh sliced mushrooms 1 tsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 onion, diced 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tsp olive oil 2 lbs. angel hair pasta Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Directions Place pan of water on stove med. high heat to boil water, add a small amount of salt.</description></item><item><title>Simple and Tasty Potato Wedges</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-and-tasty-potato-wedges/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-and-tasty-potato-wedges/</guid><description>Try these easy potato wedges made from red, russet, or sweet potatoes. Simply cut wedges, butter, season, and bake. Potato wedges are a great snack or side dish for any main entree.
Potato Wedges Ingredients serves 6-10
4 large potatoes 1/4 c butter, melted 1/4 c grated Parmesan cheese Chef Frank’s Seasoning to taste garlic to taste(granulated or fresh chopped) Potato Wedges Directions Cut potatoes the long way into wedges(about 3-4 per halve).</description></item></channel></rss>