<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>200 people on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>/tags/200-people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 200 people on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/200-people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apple Bread For 200 Recipe</title>
      <link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-bread-for-200-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-bread-for-200-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Our apple bread recipe is easy to make about a 15 minute prep time. This recipe from scratch will keep your clients happy. Apple quick bread for 200 will enhance any breakfast and makes great muffins too.
Apple Bread Or Muffins For 200 Prep time: 15-20 minutes
Bake time: 40 minutes
Yield: 280 pieces
Apple Bread Ingredients  2 #10 cans sliced apples (chop up to marble size pieces) 20 c sugar 10 c vegetable oil 40 eggs 2 tbsp vanilla 1 tbsp salt 2 tbsp cinnamon 1 c milk 40 c flour 3 tbsp baking powder 3 tbsp baking soda  Apple Bread Directions In large 60 qt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Crisp For 200</title>
      <link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-crisp-for-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-crisp-for-200/</guid>
      <description>Kids and adults love apple crisp for dessert. So easy to make and goes with any meal. Schools, camps, and churches love this recipe.
Apple Crisp for 200 People Apple Ingredients  8 #10 cans sliced apples (water pack) 16 c. sugar 16 tbs corn starch 8 tbs cinnamon 8- 2″ full size hotel pans  Apple Directions place 1 can apples, (do not drain) in each pan and even out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Baked Ham Recipe For 200</title>
      <link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/honey-baked-ham-recipe-for-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/honey-baked-ham-recipe-for-200/</guid>
      <description>Delicious honey baked ham for 200 with a quick 15 minute prep time and 1 hour cook time is easy for large group meals. Honey baked ham recipe has honey, clove, brown sugar, and applesauce, very delicious!
Honey Baked Ham for 200 Recipe Ingredients  45# whole ham (flat buffet)sliced 1/4 inch thick 5 tsp ground clove 4 c honey 10 c applesauce 8 c brown sugar  Directions In shallow hotel pans, shingle ham.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalloped Corn Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/scalloped-corn-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/scalloped-corn-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Scalloped Corn is quite an easy institutional recipe to prepare for large groups and accompanies many entrees. Scalloped Corn for 200 will hold for several hours in a warmer at 140℉ – 165℉.
Scalloped Corn for 200 Ingredients  8 #10 cans cans creamed corn 30 eggs 2 lbs saltines (crushed) 2 lbs butter (melted) 2 c. milk 2 tbs pepper (avoid salt as saltines contain enough)  Directions In large mixing bowl add corn, 1 1/2 lbs crackers (crushed), eggs, butter, and milk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spaghetti Sauce Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>/institutional-recipes-for-200/spaghetti-sauce-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/institutional-recipes-for-200/spaghetti-sauce-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Our Spaghetti Sauce Recipe for 200 People will guarantee success for your large group meal. Fresh ground beef, herbs and spicesand tomato sauce make our spaghetti sauce for 200 a hit! A quick easy recipe. Simply omit the ground beef for a fantastic vegetarian recipe!
Spaghetti Sauce for 200 Ingredients  40# ground beef, cooked, drained (optional) 8- #10 cans tomato sauce 1- #10 can tomato paste 4 onions, diced 1/2 c chopped garlic,fresh or dehydrated 2 green peppers, diced 2# fresh sliced mushrooms 1 c brown sugar 1/2 c soy sauce 1 c leaf oregano 1/2 c basil, (1 cup if fresh) 2 tbsp ground rosemary 1 tbsp white pepper 20 bay leaves, whole (to be removed before serving)  Directions Prepare ground beef and sauce in intervals together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
