<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pork on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/pork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pork on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:30:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/pork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Honey Barbecue Sauce Recipe</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Honey Barbecue Sauce Recipe Try Chef Frank’s Homemade Honey Barbecue Sauce when you’re grilling outside in the summer or cooking inside when it’s not so warm out. This sauce makes your ribs, chicken, or steak come alive with the sweet taste of local honey.
Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients  1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses  Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Barbecue Country Ribs</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</guid>
      <description>Chef Frank’s honey barbecue country ribs are slow cooked until tender and will wow your family and friends at yourback yard Barbecue.
Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Ingredients  3 lb country pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 to 2 c honey barbecue sauce 1/2 c water  Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning. Cover and roast at 275* for 2 -1/2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</guid>
      <description>Chef Frank’s Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs are so delicious and easy to prepare in the oven or on the barbecue grill. Great with roasted red potatoesand salador fruit.
Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Ingredients  3 lb or more baby back pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 c honey barbecue sauce 1 c barbecue sauce (if you prefer regular barbecue sauce without honey) 1/2 c water  Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Roast with Michigan Apples</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</guid>
      <description>Slow cooked pork roast with fresh Michigan apples and spices. Tender and juicy and served with stuffing or potatoes, salad and of course, our satisfying desserts.
Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Ingredients Serves 5 – 8
 3 lb pork shoulder roast or fresh ham 1 medium onion 2 Michigan apples, peeled cut in chunks 1/2 c applesauce 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp sage 1/2 tsp black pepper 1 c water  Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Directions Place roast in roasting pan, place all ingredients on top of roast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuffed Pork Loin Recipe</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Stuffed pork loin with fresh raspberry sauce is a wonderful Holiday or Fall entree. The stuffing can be made with either walnuts or pecans. for presentation, slice and shingle onto a platter or tray.
Stuffed Pork Loin With Raspberry Sauce Stuffing:  4 c water 2tsp chicken base 1/2 lg. onion diced 2 ribs celery diced 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tbsp sage 2 apples, peeled, diced 1/2 stick butter 1 c chopped pecans  Place all ingredients above in medium sauce pan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
