<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kids Corner Recipes on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Kids Corner Recipes on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:12:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Easy No Bake Cookies</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/easy-no-bake-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/easy-no-bake-cookies/</guid><description>Quick No Bake Cookies Recipe are a standard for Holidaysor any day. No Bake cookies in your lunch bag put a smile on your face. There’s chocolate in it ya know!Skippy Loves No Bake Cookies!No Bake Cookies Recipe 1/2 c margerine 1/2 c milk 1/2 c cocoa 2 c sugar 1/2 tsp salt No Bake Cookies Directions place these ingredients in sauce pan and heat to a slow boil.</description></item><item><title>Easy Egg In A Basket</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/easy-egg-in-a-basket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:27:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/easy-egg-in-a-basket/</guid><description>Quick Egg in a Basket Recipe is fun for the kids to eat and help make. Pictures to guide you when making egg in a basket, a great fun breakfast.
Egg In A Basket Recipe 1 slice bread 1 egg 2 pats butter Egg In A Basket Directions Butter bread lightly on both sides. Place small fry pan on stove and turn on low heat. Lightly grill bread on both sides.</description></item><item><title>Old Fashioned Macaroni and Cheese Recipe</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/old-fashioned-macaroni-and-cheese-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:56:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/old-fashioned-macaroni-and-cheese-recipe/</guid><description>Quick Macaroni and Cheese Recipe is made from Cheddar Cheese, Milk, and Butter, like Mom used to make. Macaroni and Cheese for Lunch or Dinner is a Winner that Kids and Adults Love.
Macaroni and Cheese Ingredients Serves 8-12
2 lb macaroni 2 lb shredded cheddar cheese (sharp) 1 1/2 c milk 2 oz. butter melted or soft salt and pepper to taste Macaroni and Cheese Directions Boil macaroni for 8 minutes, drain.</description></item><item><title>Apple Smackers Recipe</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/apple-smackers-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/apple-smackers-recipe/</guid><description>Apple Smackers Recipe Serves 4
3 tart apples 3 tbsp sugar 1/2 tbsp cinnamon 2 0z. butter, melted Apple Smackers Directions Peel apples and cut in wedges. Place wedges on microwaveable plate. Brush melted butter over apples. Combine sugar with cinnamon, then sprinkle over apples. Cover with wax paper or plastic wrap and place in microwave for about 5 minutes. Check for tenderness. Eat em up.</description></item><item><title>Kids’ Pita Pizza Recipe</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/kids-pita-pizza-recipe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 02:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/kids-pita-pizza-recipe/</guid><description>Kids Pita Pizza Recipe is Perfect for Birthday Parties, Pic-nics and Special Events. Kids can help make Pita Pizza, it’s fun!
Pita Pizza Ingredients (for individual pizzas) serves 10 10 pita breads (flat breads) 2 c pizza sauce 1 1/2 lb mozzerella cheese( shredded) 1/2 onion, diced 1 green pepper, diced 2 c mushrooms, sliced 1/2 c black olives, sliced 8 oz. sliced pepperoni 8 oz. ham, diced 8 oz.</description></item><item><title>People Chow – Kids and Adults Snack</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/people-chow-kids-and-adults-snack/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/people-chow-kids-and-adults-snack/</guid><description>Quick People Chow Recipe is a favorite among kids and adults alike. People Chow has chocolate and peanut butter goodness. A great Birthday treat!
People Chow Recipe 1 c margerine or butter 1 c peanut butter 1 bag chocolate chips 1 box rice chex cereal 1 c powdered sugar Directions Mix all ingredients except powdered sugar in a large bowl. Once all is mixed, place in large paper bag with powdered sugar, fold closed and shake vigorously.</description></item><item><title>Microwave Caramel Corn</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/microwave-caramel-corn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/microwave-caramel-corn/</guid><description>This quick and easy microwave caramel corn recipe is a hit with kids and adults alike. Microwave caramel corn is a fun project to do with kids on those cold winter days.
Microwave Caramel Corn Recipe 3-5 qts. popped corn. Place in non-stick sprayed paper grocery bag. Caramel Recipe 1/4 c corn syrup 1 c brown sugar 1 stick butter 1 tsp vanilla 1/2 tsp baking soda Direction Melt and cook in microwave for 4 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Easy Cinnamon Crunchies</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/easy-cinnamon-crunchies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 01:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/kids-corner-recipes/easy-cinnamon-crunchies/</guid><description>Quick Cinnamon Crunchies are an Easy Recipe for after school snacks or a kids party. Easy Cinnamon Crunchies from pie crust, butter, cinnamon, and sugar. Eat them warm.
Skippy loves kids and wants you to learn to cook these great foods! There’s more recipes to come!
Cinnamon Crunchies Ingredients 1 pkg pie crust 1/4 c butter, melted 1 tbsp cinnamon 1/2 c sugar Cinnamon Crunchies Directions Open pie crust and lay out on cookie sheet.</description></item></channel></rss>