<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Comfort Food on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/comfort-food/</link><description>Recent content in Comfort Food on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/comfort-food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chicken Noodle Casserole</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</guid><description>Chicken Noodle Casserole, Quick Recipe for Lunch or Dinner Entree. Chicken Noodle Casserole is True Comfort Food and goes with any Salad, Fruit, and Warm Bread.
Chicken Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
1 lb cooked chicken meat cut up1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank&amp;rsquo;s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux Chicken Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Creamy Scalloped Potatoes</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/creamy-scalloped-potatoes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/creamy-scalloped-potatoes/</guid><description>Quick Creamy Scalloped Potatoes, Great Comfort Food Entree on those Cold Winter Days. Warm up the House with a Creamy Scalloped Potato Aroma.
Creamy Scalloped Potatoes serves 8
3# red potatoes, sliced 1/4″ 1/2 onion, diced 3 ribs celery, diced small 3 c milk 1 c roux 1 tsp chicken base 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 oz. butter Creamy Scalloped Potatoes Directions Boil potatoes in medium size pot for about 20 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Scalloped Potatoes – Grandma’s Comfort Food</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scalloped-potatoes-grandmas-comfort-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scalloped-potatoes-grandmas-comfort-food/</guid><description>Quick Scalloped Potatoes is Grandma’s recipe and will satisfy any appetite. Add ham to this Scalloped Potato recipe for a wonderful comfort food a cold winter day.
Scalloped Potatoes Ingredients Scalloped Potatoes 6 potatoes, peeled, thin sliced 1/2 onion, diced 2 rib celery, diced 4 oz. butter, melted 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 cups flour 3 cups milk Scalloped Potatoes Directions In large casserole dish, place a layer of potatoes in bottom.</description></item></channel></rss>