<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beef on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/beef/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beef on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/beef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick and Easy Chili Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/quick-and-easy-chili-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/quick-and-easy-chili-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Try this Quick chili recipe for school kid’s lunch or a church function. Corn bread and shredded cheddar cheese along with a saladmake this a great meal and is very affordable as well.
Here’s the chili recipe for those of you cooking for a crowd:
Ingredients  56# chili beans(red) ( 7 no. 10 cans) 11 qts tomato juice 30# ground beef 6 large green peppers diced 4 large spanish onions diced 2 large stalks celery diced 1 c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Hot Dogs</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/blog/2021-08-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/blog/2021-08-22/</guid>
      <description>There is nothing like a fine summer hot dog. some of the best recipes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Barbecue Sauce</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/homemade-barbecue-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/homemade-barbecue-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Prepare this wonderful barbecue sauce on the stove. Great for grilling outside or in. Use our sauce for chicken, ribs, pork, or barbecue sandwiches. Chef Frank finishes this recipe off with red wine for an added kick!
Barbecue Sauce Recipe  2 c ketchup 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses  Barbecue Sauce Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe Basics and Sauces</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Recipe Basics Section of our site. Recipe Basics Partner and Link With Other Recipes on This Site. A Convenient and Quick way to Coordinate your Family Menu Plans. For Example, Maitre d’ Butter Goes with Sirloin Steak., Easy Basic Sauce Recipes, Easy Internal Links to the Roux Recipe, Egg Washfor your Fruit Pie Crusts so your Pie Crust is Flaky. Drawn Butter, for Fresh Seafood Recipes like Lobster Thermidorand Broiled Whitefishfrom Lake Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Homemade Bread</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/easy-homemade-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/easy-homemade-bread/</guid>
      <description>Quick Whole Wheat or White Bread Recipe is From Scratch, Makes Two Loaves, and is the same as Grandma Makes. Homemade Bread Aroma Welcomes Your Family and Guests Warmly.
Homemade Bread Ingredients  6-7 c flour ( whole wheat or white) 3 level tbsp yeast paste, or dry yeast 2 tbsp sugar 1 tbsp honey 1 tbsp salt 1 c 2% milk 1 1/4 c water warm 95℉ 2 tsp butter  Homemade Bread Directions In a large mixing bowl place warm water (95℉), then yeast and mix together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Barbecue Sauce Recipe</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Honey Barbecue Sauce Recipe Try Chef Frank’s Homemade Honey Barbecue Sauce when you’re grilling outside in the summer or cooking inside when it’s not so warm out. This sauce makes your ribs, chicken, or steak come alive with the sweet taste of local honey.
Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients  1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses  Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goulash With Ground Beef</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/casserole-recipes/goulash-with-ground-beef/</guid>
      <description>Quick Goulash Recipe with Fresh Ground Beef and Elbow Macaroni, Tomato Sauce and Fresh Cut Vegetables with Cheese. Goulash is a Great Casserole for Lunch or Supper.
Goulash serves 8
 1 lb macaroni, cooked 8 min., drained 1 lb ground beef, cooked, drained 1/2 onion, diced 1/2 green pepper, diced 1 can tomato sauce 1 can diced tomatoes 2 oz. melted butter 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp chili powder 1 c shredded cheddar cheese(optional)  Combine all ingredients in large mixing bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Prime Rib Roast with Au Jus</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/holiday-prime-rib-roast-with-au-jus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/holiday-prime-rib-roast-with-au-jus/</guid>
      <description>Celebrate the Holidays with our very special Prime Rib Roast recipe. It includes an awesome Au Jus recipe. Follow the links to festive side dishes too.
Prime Rib Roast Ingredients  15-19 lb rib roast 1/4 c garlic, fresh chopped 1 tbsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 c water  Prime Rib Directions Place rib roast in large roasting pan, bone down, add water and seasonings. Cover and place in oven at 275* and roast for 5 hours then check with thermometer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
