<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Summer on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/summer/</link><description>Recent content in Summer on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/summer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Summer Hot Dogs</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/blog/2021-08-22/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/blog/2021-08-22/</guid><description>There is nothing like a fine summer hot dog. some of the best recipes</description></item><item><title>Hello world!</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 02:18:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/hello-world/</guid><description>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</description></item><item><title>Don’t Crowd Me!</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/dont-crowd-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/dont-crowd-me/</guid><description>I was thinking about crowding the other day as I sat on bleachers in the gym waiting to hear our grandson sing for his class Christmas concert. It was uncomfortable and hot, with little room to relax your arms or stretch your legs. It was all worth it when our grandson was on stage singing and shyly smiling as he noticed us in the audience. After the concert I started thinking about food crowding and how it challenges the quality of a recipe.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Summer Cucumber Salad</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/fresh-summer-cucumber-salad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/fresh-summer-cucumber-salad/</guid><description>Fresh from the garden comes this wonderful cucumber salad with fresh summer garden tomato, and onion. Simple and delicious for steak or rib cookouts and family meals.
Cucumber Salad – Fresh Summer Garden Salad Ingredients 1 large seedless cucumber 1/2 large sweet onion 1 fresh tomato 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 3 c. apple cider vineager 1 tbsp sugar 1/2 c. water Cucumber Salad – Fresh Summer Garden Salad Directions Cut vegetables into large chunks (bite size) and place into right sized bowl.</description></item><item><title>Honey Barbecue Country Ribs</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</guid><description>Chef Frank’s honey barbecue country ribs are slow cooked until tender and will wow your family and friends at yourback yard Barbecue.
Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Ingredients 3 lb country pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 to 2 c honey barbecue sauce 1/2 c water Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning. Cover and roast at 275* for 2 -1/2 hours.</description></item><item><title>Vegetarian Honey Barbecue Sauce</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/vegetarian-honey-barbecue-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/vegetarian-honey-barbecue-sauce/</guid><description>Prepare this vegetarian honey barbecue sauce recipe when you’re grilling outside or cooking inside. It makes your vegetarian burgers, and ribs taste amazing.
Vegetarian Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item></channel></rss>