<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bread on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/bread/</link><description>Recent content in Bread on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/bread/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Easy Bread Recipes</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/</guid><description>Baking bread doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to be difficult. It is easy to make, easy to clean, and is one of the best ways to easily have a fresh loaf of bread to serve for breakfast or dinner. So whether you need a quick and easy recipe for a bread starter or just want to learn how to bake bread, you&amp;rsquo;re on the right blog. Here are some easy recipes.</description></item><item><title>Apple Bread For 200 Recipe</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-bread-for-200-recipe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-bread-for-200-recipe/</guid><description>Our apple bread recipe is easy to make about a 15 minute prep time. This recipe from scratch will keep your clients happy. Apple quick bread for 200 will enhance any breakfast and makes great muffins too.
Apple Bread Or Muffins For 200 Prep time: 15-20 minutes
Bake time: 40 minutes
Yield: 280 pieces
Apple Bread Ingredients 2 #10 cans sliced apples (chop up to marble size pieces) 20 c sugar 10 c vegetable oil 40 eggs 2 tbsp vanilla 1 tbsp salt 2 tbsp cinnamon 1 c milk 40 c flour 3 tbsp baking powder 3 tbsp baking soda Apple Bread Directions In large 60 qt.</description></item><item><title>Banana Bread And Muffins Recipe For 200 People</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/banana-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/banana-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</guid><description>Banana Bread Recipe For 200 Quick Banana Bread or Muffins for 280 People. This Quick Institutional Scratch Recipe will keep your clients happy. Use the same Quick Banana Bread Recipe for Muffins.
Prep time: 15-20 minutes
Bake time: 40 minutes
Yield: 280 pieces
Banana Bread Ingredients 60 ripe peeled bananas 20 c sugar 10 c vegetable oil 40 eggs 2 tbsp vanilla 1 tbsp salt 1 c milk 40 c flour 3 tbsp baking powder 3 tbsp baking soda Banana Bread Directions In large 60 qt.</description></item><item><title>Easy Homemade Bread</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/easy-homemade-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/easy-homemade-bread/</guid><description>Quick Whole Wheat or White Bread Recipe is From Scratch, Makes Two Loaves, and is the same as Grandma Makes. Homemade Bread Aroma Welcomes Your Family and Guests Warmly.
Homemade Bread Ingredients 6-7 c flour ( whole wheat or white) 3 level tbsp yeast paste, or dry yeast 2 tbsp sugar 1 tbsp honey 1 tbsp salt 1 c 2% milk 1 1/4 c water warm 95℉ 2 tsp butter Homemade Bread Directions In a large mixing bowl place warm water (95℉), then yeast and mix together.</description></item><item><title>Zucchini Bread Recipe</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/zucchini-bread-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:04:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/zucchini-bread-recipe/</guid><description>Easy Zucchini Quick Bread Recipe is a favorite in the Summer after Harvesting Fresh Zucchini from the Garden. Zucchini Bread with Nuts Too, and even Dried Fruit, Just add to the Recipe.
Zucchini Bread Ingredients 3 eggs 2 1/2 c sugar 1 c oil 3 c flour 3 tsp cinnamon 1 tsp salt 1 tsp baking powder 1 tsp baking soda 3 tsp vanilla extract 4 c shredded zucchini 1 c chopped nuts (walnuts or pecans) Zucchini Bread Directions Blend together eggs, oil, salt, vanilla, and zucchini.</description></item><item><title>Poppy Seed Bread Recipe</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/poppy-seed-bread-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/poppy-seed-bread-recipe/</guid><description>Poppy Seed Bread
Poppy Seed Bread is an old Family Favorite Quick Bread Recipe. So Easy to Prepare, Poppy Seed Bread with a Hint of Lemon is Wonderful for Breakfast or a Quick Dessert.
Poppy Seed Bread Ingredients 1 pkg. yellow cake mix 1 pkg. toasted coconut instant pudding 4 large eggs 1/2 c vegetable oil 1/4 c soaked and drained poppy seeds 1 c hot water Poppy Seed Bread Directions Mix all ingredients in large bowl, beat as for cake.</description></item><item><title>Sandwich Recipes</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/sandwich-recipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:22:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/sandwich-recipes/</guid><description>Welcome to our Sandwich Section. Have Lunch at Home with Fine Restaurant Style Quality Sandwiches. Scrumptious Open Faced or Grilled restaurant Style Sandwiches like French Dips with Au Jus, English Rarebits, or Grilled Ham And Cheese to Patty Melts. Then go to our Soup Section for Homemade Soups to go with these Simple Delicious Sandwiches.
Sandwich Recipes Sloppy Joes, Quick and Easy
Coney Sauce, Original Recipe
Grilled Sandwiches
Restaurant Sandwiches</description></item><item><title>Fool Proof Banana Bread</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</guid><description>Banana Bread Homemade banana bread is truly foolproof and will only take a few minutes to prepare. Take advantage of variations to this recipe by adding nuts of your choice. 1 Hour in the oven and everyone is enjoying warm banana bread!
3 ripe bananas 2 eggs 1 c sugar 1/2 c oil 2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/4 tsp salt dash milk 1 tsp vanills ext.</description></item></channel></rss>