<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bread on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>/tags/bread/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bread on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:01:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/bread/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Poppy Seed Bread Recipe</title>
      <link>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/poppy-seed-bread-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/poppy-seed-bread-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Poppy Seed Bread is an old Family Favorite Quick Bread Recipe. So Easy to Prepare, Poppy Seed Bread with a Hint of Lemon is Wonderful for Breakfast or a Quick Dessert.
Poppy Seed Bread Ingredients  1 pkg. yellow cake mix 1 pkg. toasted coconut instant pudding 4 large eggs 1/2 c vegetable oil 1/4 c soaked and drained poppy seeds 1 c hot water  Poppy Seed Bread Directions Mix all ingredients in large bowl, beat as for cake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandwich Recipes</title>
      <link>/recipes/sandwich-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/sandwich-recipes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our Sandwich Section. Have Lunch at Home with Fine Restaurant Style Quality Sandwiches. Scrumptious Open Faced or Grilled restaurant Style Sandwiches like French Dips with Au Jus, English Rarebits, or Grilled Ham And Cheese to Patty Melts. Then go to our Soup Section for Homemade Soups to go with these Simple Delicious Sandwiches.
Sandwich Recipes Sloppy Joes, Quick and Easy
Coney Sauce, Original Recipe
Grilled Sandwiches
Restaurant Sandwiches</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fool Proof Banana Bread</title>
      <link>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</guid>
      <description>Banana Bread Homemade banana bread is truly foolproof and will only take a few minutes to prepare. Take advantage of variations to this recipe by adding nuts of your choice. 1 Hour in the oven and everyone is enjoying warm banana bread!
 3 ripe bananas 2 eggs 1 c sugar 1/2 c oil 2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/4 tsp salt dash milk 1 tsp vanills ext.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
