<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Barbecue on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/barbecue/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Barbecue on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:31:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/barbecue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Barbecue Sauce</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/homemade-barbecue-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/homemade-barbecue-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Prepare this wonderful barbecue sauce on the stove. Great for grilling outside or in. Use our sauce for chicken, ribs, pork, or barbecue sandwiches. Chef Frank finishes this recipe off with red wine for an added kick!
Barbecue Sauce Recipe  2 c ketchup 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses  Barbecue Sauce Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Barbecue Country Ribs</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecue-country-ribs/</guid>
      <description>Chef Frank’s honey barbecue country ribs are slow cooked until tender and will wow your family and friends at yourback yard Barbecue.
Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Ingredients  3 lb country pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 to 2 c honey barbecue sauce 1/2 c water  Honey Barbecue Country Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning. Cover and roast at 275* for 2 -1/2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-barbecued-baby-back-ribs/</guid>
      <description>Chef Frank’s Honey Barbecued Baby Back Ribs are so delicious and easy to prepare in the oven or on the barbecue grill. Great with roasted red potatoesand salador fruit.
Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Ingredients  3 lb or more baby back pork ribs 1/2 onion, cut chunky 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning pinch white pepper 1 c honey barbecue sauce 1 c barbecue sauce (if you prefer regular barbecue sauce without honey) 1/2 c water  Honey Barbecue Baby Back Ribs Directions In roasting pan, place ribs, water, onion, and seasoning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Our honey teriyaki barbecue sauce will become a staple in your recipe file. It’s easy to prepare on the stove and great for the barbecue grillfor ribs, chicken, chops and steaks.
Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce Ingredients  2 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 3 tbsp soy sauce 1 c pineapple juice ( or 1 c, pureed fresh pineapple) 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses 2 tbsp grape jelly  Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour or until reduced, stirring frequently.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
