<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stuffing on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/stuffing/</link><description>Recent content in Stuffing on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/stuffing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pork Roast with Michigan Apples</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</guid><description>Slow cooked pork roast with fresh Michigan apples and spices. Tender and juicy and served with stuffing or potatoes, salad and of course, our satisfying desserts.
Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Ingredients Serves 5 – 8
3 lb pork shoulder roast or fresh ham 1 medium onion 2 Michigan apples, peeled cut in chunks 1/2 c applesauce 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp sage 1/2 tsp black pepper 1 c water Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Directions Place roast in roasting pan, place all ingredients on top of roast.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Turkey Recipes For The Holidays</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-turkey-recipes-for-the-holidays/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-turkey-recipes-for-the-holidays/</guid><description>Fill your house with the aroma of our festive oven roasted turkey. Wonderful for family celebrations and Holiday meals.
Oven Roasted Turkey Ingredients 20-25 lb turkey (Thawed if frozen 2-3 days in fridge) rinse under cold water before cooking 3 tbs rubbed sage 3 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 3 tbsp melted butter 2 c water Roasted Turkey Directions In large roasting pan place turkey, breast side up. Brush with melted butter, then rub with sage.</description></item><item><title>Slow Roasted Cornish Game Hen</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/slow-roasted-cornish-game-hen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/slow-roasted-cornish-game-hen/</guid><description>Wonderful Cornish game hen, slow roasted and stuffed with apple walnut sage stuffing, or plain roasted served with wild rice. This recipe makes Holidays or any day special.
Slow Roasted Cornish Game Hen Ingredients Non-Stuffed Cornish Game Hen 1 Cornish game hen per serving as follows:
2 tbs melted butter 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp rubbed sage pepper to taste thoroughly rinse with cold water, pat dry, then place game hens in roasting pan back side down.</description></item></channel></rss>