<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fresh Herbs on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>/tags/fresh-herbs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fresh Herbs on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/fresh-herbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick and Easy Egg Noodle Recipe</title>
      <link>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/quick-and-easy-egg-noodle-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/quick-and-easy-egg-noodle-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Our quick egg noodle recipe is great for homemade soups or casseroles. Add fresh chopped herbs in the flour for flavored noodles, and use whole wheat flour for better nutrition.
Egg Noodles Ingredients  4 whole eggs pinch salt or Chef Frank’s Seasoning 4 cups flour (whole wheat flour for more nutrition) optional fresh chopped herbs can be mixed with flour like sage, thyme, oregano, marjoram, etc. 2 tsp ice water  Egg Noodles Directions combine flour, eggs and salt, in mixer with dough hook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Turkey Recipes For The Holidays</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-turkey-recipes-for-the-holidays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-turkey-recipes-for-the-holidays/</guid>
      <description>Fill your house with the aroma of our festive oven roasted turkey. Wonderful for family celebrations and Holiday meals.
Oven Roasted Turkey Ingredients  20-25 lb turkey (Thawed if frozen 2-3 days in fridge) rinse under cold water before cooking 3 tbs rubbed sage 3 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 3 tbsp melted butter 2 c water  Roasted Turkey Directions In large roasting pan place turkey, breast side up. Brush with melted butter, then rub with sage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thyme Chicken Breast Entree</title>
      <link>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/thyme-chicken-breast-entree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/thyme-chicken-breast-entree/</guid>
      <description>Thyme chicken breast is prepared with fresh thyme, herbs and spices, then baked in the oven. It makes a good partner to wild rice, or roasted red potatoes, corn bread, salad or fruit.
Thyme Chicken Breast Ingredients serves 4
 4 Chicken breasts, boneless 1 tbsp crushed thyme 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 oz. Maitre d’ butter
(Click link or see recipe below)  Thyme Chicken Breast Directions ### Oven Method: Place chicken breasts on greased sheet pan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
