<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chicken on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/chicken/</link><description>Recent content in Chicken on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:30:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/chicken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Honey Barbecue Sauce Recipe</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 14:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/recipe-basics-and-sauces/honey-barbecue-sauce-recipe/</guid><description>Honey Barbecue Sauce Recipe Try Chef Frank’s Homemade Honey Barbecue Sauce when you’re grilling outside in the summer or cooking inside when it’s not so warm out. This sauce makes your ribs, chicken, or steak come alive with the sweet taste of local honey.
Honey Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 1 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tbsp season salt 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 1/8 c vinegar 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses Directions Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Noodle Casserole</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/chicken-noodle-casserole/</guid><description>Chicken Noodle Casserole, Quick Recipe for Lunch or Dinner Entree. Chicken Noodle Casserole is True Comfort Food and goes with any Salad, Fruit, and Warm Bread.
Chicken Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
1 lb cooked chicken meat cut up1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank&amp;rsquo;s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux Chicken Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Delicious Homemade Teriyaki Chicken</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/delicious-homemade-teriyaki-chicken/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/delicious-homemade-teriyaki-chicken/</guid><description>Teriyaki chicken with homemade sauce contains pineapple, garlic, brown sugar and soy sauce. It’s great for the barbecue grill outside, or inside under your broiler. Teriyaki chicken can be served with wild rice, salads or fruits or all the above.
Great on the barbecue grill!
Teriyaki Chicken Ingredients serves 4-6
2 whole chickens cut in 1/8’s, fresh 2 c Teriyaki sauce (see recipe below) 1 tbs. Chef Frank’s Seasoning Method #1 In large roasting pan, place chicken, seasoning, and teriyaki sauce.</description></item><item><title>Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/honey-teriyaki-barbecue-sauce/</guid><description>Our honey teriyaki barbecue sauce will become a staple in your recipe file. It’s easy to prepare on the stove and great for the barbecue grillfor ribs, chicken, chops and steaks.
Honey Teriyaki Barbecue Sauce Ingredients 2 c ketchup 1/2 c honey 1 tbsp yellow mustard 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1/2 onion small diced 1 tbsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 c brown sugar 3 tbsp soy sauce 1 c pineapple juice ( or 1 c, pureed fresh pineapple) 2 tbsp Italian herb seasoning 1 tsp ground rosemary 1/2 c red wine 1/8 c molasses 2 tbsp grape jelly Combine ingredients in sauce pan, simmer for 1/2 hour or until reduced, stirring frequently.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Chicken Entree</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-chicken-entree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/roasted-chicken-entree/</guid><description>Roast chicken is a quick recipe for a nice supper. All of our side dish recipes are compatible, and hot rolls with butter tops it off.
Roasted Chicken For 4 1 whole chicken (rinsed) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp sage (rubbed) black pepper to taste 1 tsp garlic (granulated or fresh chopped) 3 tbsp butter (melted) Roasted Chicken Directions Place chicken breast side up in roaster pan.</description></item><item><title>Simple Lime Chicken Entree</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-lime-chicken-entree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/simple-lime-chicken-entree/</guid><description>Delicious lime chicken, southwest style, made from cut up chicken or boneless breasts. Fresh lime and zest with Chef Frank’s Seasoning, puts it over the top!
Lime Chicken Ingredients 1 chicken cut in 1/8’s or ( 8 chicken breasts) boneless skinless 4 limes or 4 tbsp lime juice 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp southwest or tex mex seasoning 1 tsp paprika 2 tbsp melted butter 1 lime for lime zest (peel skin and slice very thin, place over chicken before cooking) Lime Chicken Directions Baking Method Place chicken in baking dish.</description></item><item><title>Thyme Chicken Breast Entree</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/thyme-chicken-breast-entree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/thyme-chicken-breast-entree/</guid><description>Thyme chicken breast is prepared with fresh thyme, herbs and spices, then baked in the oven. It makes a good partner to wild rice, or roasted red potatoes, corn bread, salad or fruit.
Thyme Chicken Breast Ingredients serves 4
4 Chicken breasts, boneless 1 tbsp crushed thyme 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 oz. Maitre d’ butter
(Click link or see recipe below) Thyme Chicken Breast Directions ### Oven Method: Place chicken breasts on greased sheet pan.</description></item></channel></rss>