<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Desserts on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/desserts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Desserts on Chef Frank&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/desserts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Banana Bread And Muffins Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/banana-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/banana-bread-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Banana Bread Recipe For 200 Quick Banana Bread or Muffins for 280 People. This Quick Institutional Scratch Recipe will keep your clients happy. Use the same Quick Banana Bread Recipe for Muffins.
Prep time: 15-20 minutes
Bake time: 40 minutes
Yield: 280 pieces
Banana Bread Ingredients  60 ripe peeled bananas 20 c sugar 10 c vegetable oil 40 eggs 2 tbsp vanilla 1 tbsp salt 1 c milk 40 c flour 3 tbsp baking powder 3 tbsp baking soda  Banana Bread Directions In large 60 qt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate Chip Cookies Recipe For 200 People</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/chocolate-chip-cookies-recipe-for-200-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/chocolate-chip-cookies-recipe-for-200-people/</guid>
      <description>Real Chocolate Chip Cookies are Quick and Easy Scratch Cookies to make for Gatherings, Large Groups, Camps, or Schools. Kids love them and will want them again! Quick Institutional Recipe.
Real Chocolate Chip Cookies Recipe for 200 People Ingredients  4 lbs. butter softened 16 eggs 6 c. brown sugar 6 c. sugar 20 c. flour 2 tbs vanilla 2 tbs baking powder 2 tbs baking soda 2 tsp salt 24 c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Roast with Michigan Apples</title>
      <link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/pork-roast-with-michigan-apples/</guid>
      <description>Slow cooked pork roast with fresh Michigan apples and spices. Tender and juicy and served with stuffing or potatoes, salad and of course, our satisfying desserts.
Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Ingredients Serves 5 – 8
 3 lb pork shoulder roast or fresh ham 1 medium onion 2 Michigan apples, peeled cut in chunks 1/2 c applesauce 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tsp sage 1/2 tsp black pepper 1 c water  Pork Roast With Michigan Apples Directions Place roast in roasting pan, place all ingredients on top of roast.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
