<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nuts on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/nuts/</link><description>Recent content in Nuts on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:09:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/nuts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>All Sweet Nut Cookies</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/dessert-recipes/all-sweet-nut-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 17:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/dessert-recipes/all-sweet-nut-cookies/</guid><description>Sandy’s allsweet nut cookies are fun and easy to make. A great snack for kids after school or anytime. Get the kids to help make these delicious cookies.
Sandy’s Allsweet Nut Cookies 1/2 c. margerine softened 2 tsp sugar 1 c. chopped pecans 1 tsp. vanilla 7/8 c. sifted flour 2 c. powdered sugar set aside (for rolling cookies after baking) Allsweet Nut Cookies Directions Cream margarine and sugar together.</description></item><item><title>Zucchini Bread Recipe</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/zucchini-bread-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:04:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/zucchini-bread-recipe/</guid><description>Zucchini Bread Recipe Easy Zucchini Quick Bread Recipe is a favorite in the Summer after Harvesting Fresh Zucchini from the Garden. Zucchini Bread with Nuts Too, and even Dried Fruit, Just add to the Recipe.
Zucchini Bread Ingredients 3 eggs 2 1/2 c sugar 1 c oil 3 c flour 3 tsp cinnamon 1 tsp salt 1 tsp baking powder 1 tsp baking soda 3 tsp vanilla extract 4 c shredded zucchini 1 c chopped nuts (walnuts or pecans) Zucchini Bread Directions Blend together eggs, oil, salt, vanilla, and zucchini.</description></item><item><title>Stuffed Pork Loin Recipe</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/stuffed-pork-loin-recipe/</guid><description>Stuffed pork loin with fresh raspberry sauce is a wonderful Holiday or Fall entree. The stuffing can be made with either walnuts or pecans. for presentation, slice and shingle onto a platter or tray.
Stuffed Pork Loin With Raspberry Sauce Stuffing: 4 c water 2tsp chicken base 1/2 lg. onion diced 2 ribs celery diced 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tbsp sage 2 apples, peeled, diced 1/2 stick butter 1 c chopped pecans Place all ingredients above in medium sauce pan.</description></item></channel></rss>