<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Seafood on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/seafood/</link><description>Recent content in Seafood on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/tags/seafood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scallops Newburg With Buttery Cream Sauce</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scallops-newburg-with-buttery-cream-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/scallops-newburg-with-buttery-cream-sauce/</guid><description>Make scallops newburg with large Sea Scallops and a buttery cream sauce. Then place over rice and serve with Broccoli and cheese and a Salad. A nice mellow white wine compliments this meal.
Scallops Newburg Ingredients 2 lbs scallops (large size is better) 1/4 c small diced onion 1/4 c small diced celery 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 c roux 3 c milk 1/2 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning Scallops Newburg Directions Prepare cream sauce by heating milk and paprika over medium heat in double boiler, or carefully in sauce pan.</description></item><item><title>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/shrimp-and-angel-hair-pasta/</guid><description>Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Ingredients Serves 4
1 lb shrimp, raw, peeled, deveined, (size of your choice) 2 oz. maitre d’ butter 1/2 lb fresh sliced mushrooms 1 tsp garlic, fresh chopped 1/4 onion, diced 1 tsp. Chef Frank’s Seasoning 2 tsp olive oil 2 lbs. angel hair pasta Shrimp and Angel Hair Pasta Directions Place pan of water on stove med. high heat to boil water, add a small amount of salt.</description></item><item><title>Tuna Noodle Casserole</title><link>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.quick-e-recipes.com/chef-franks-seasoning-recipes/tuna-noodle-casserole/</guid><description>Tuna Noodle Casserole is a Family Favorite and is a Quick and Easy Recipe to Prepare. Our Creamy Tuna Noodle Casserole is Comfort Food for those Cold Winter Days.
Tuna Noodle Casserole Ingredients Serves 8
8 oz, tuna, drained 1/4 diced onion 1 rib celery cut (small horseshoe shapes) 1 tsp Chef Frank’s Seasoning 1 tbsp celery flakes 1 lb. egg noodles (boil in 4 cups water.) 1 c bread crumbs or cracker crumbs 2 c milk roux Tuna Noodle Casserole Directions Boil noodles, along with onion and celery in medium, large sauce pan.</description></item></channel></rss>