<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dessert on Chef Frank's Recipes</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/dessert/</link><description>Recent content in Dessert on Chef Frank's Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quick-e-recipes.com/tags/dessert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apple Crisp For 200</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-crisp-for-200/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/apple-crisp-for-200/</guid><description>Kids and adults love apple crisp for dessert. So easy to make and goes with any meal. Schools, camps, and churches love this recipe.
Apple Crisp for 200 People Apple Ingredients 8 #10 cans sliced apples (water pack) 16 c. sugar 16 tbs corn starch 8 tbs cinnamon 8- 2″ full size hotel pans Apple Directions place 1 can apples, (do not drain) in each pan and even out.</description></item><item><title>Easy Apple Pudding Recipe For 200 People</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/easy-apple-pudding-for-200-people/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/institutional-recipes-for-200/easy-apple-pudding-for-200-people/</guid><description>Delicious apple pudding for 200 people is a very popular dessertin the fall or for any season. Great for schools, churches and special functions.
Apple Pudding for 200 People Ingredients Apple Base Ingredients 8 – #10 cans sliced waterpack apples 16 c. sugar 16 tbs corn starch 8 tsp salt 8 tbs cinnamon Topping Ingredients 12 c. flour 5# butter, melted 5 c. brown sugar 2 tbs cinnamon 6 c.</description></item><item><title>Poppy Seed Bread Recipe</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/poppy-seed-bread-recipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/poppy-seed-bread-recipe/</guid><description>Poppy Seed Bread
Poppy Seed Bread is an old Family Favorite Quick Bread Recipe. So Easy to Prepare, Poppy Seed Bread with a Hint of Lemon is Wonderful for Breakfast or a Quick Dessert.
Poppy Seed Bread Ingredients 1 pkg. yellow cake mix 1 pkg. toasted coconut instant pudding 4 large eggs 1/2 c vegetable oil 1/4 c soaked and drained poppy seeds 1 c hot water Poppy Seed Bread Directions Mix all ingredients in large bowl, beat as for cake.</description></item><item><title>Fool Proof Banana Bread</title><link>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quick-e-recipes.com/recipes/easy-bread-recipes/fool-proof-banana-bread/</guid><description>Banana Bread Homemade banana bread is truly foolproof and will only take a few minutes to prepare. Take advantage of variations to this recipe by adding nuts of your choice. 1 Hour in the oven and everyone is enjoying warm banana bread!
3 ripe bananas 2 eggs 1 c sugar 1/2 c oil 2 c flour 1/2 tsp baking soda 1/2 tsp baking powder 1/4 tsp salt dash milk 1 tsp vanills ext.</description></item></channel></rss>